[ CHILDREN 'S VOICES ECHO HAUNTINGLY ]
Wes : MORE BLOOD !
GREAT . KEEP IT COMING . CHUCK , TERRY , PUMP AWAY .
DON 'T BE STINGY .
OK , WATCH THAT ARM . I CAN SEE THAT FAKE ARM .
OK , CHASE , KEEP THAT CLAW REALLY MOVING .
JEFFREY , JAM IT ON THERE JUST LIKE FREDDY WOULD .
GOOD , GOOD , GOOD .
AND CUT ! PRINT THAT , GRETCHEN .
Gretchen : THANK YOU , SIR . 7 ONLY .
CHASE , YOU 'RE A GENIUS .
THIS MAKES HIS OLD CLAW LOOK LIKE MOTHER TERESA 'S MITTEN .
YOU BETTER THANK THEM . THEY 'RE VERY SENSITIVE .
CHUCK , TERRY , GREAT BLOOD . OH-HO .
THANK YOU VERY MUCH .
SOME OF OUR BEST WORK .
HEY , MONKEY MAN ,
WANNA SEE SOME NEAT STUFF ?
YEAH . CHASE .
COME ON .
IT 'S ONLY MAKE-BELIEVE .
I 'LL TALK TO YOU LATER .
MARIANNE , I GOTTA GO .
OK .
LOW BRIDGE .
LET 'S SEE IF WE CAN 'T FIND SOMETHING
TO SCARE THE P.J. ' S OFF MOMMY .
HEY , HEATHER .
YOU HUNGRY , DYLAN ?
YEAH .
GRRAAH !
HEE HEE HEE HEE !
OH . GOTCHA .
IT SHOULD HAVE FLEXED MORE .
CHASE .
I THINK THE SERVOS GOT SHORTED OUT WITH BLOOD .
WELL ...
TAKE IT APART , PULL IT OUT ,
AND INSULATE THEM WITH SOME STYRO .
THE THING WASN 'T MEANT TO BE SUBMERGED , FOR PETE 'S SAKE .
I DON 'T LIKE THAT THING .
THAT THING PUTS BREAD ON OUR TABLE .
Dylan : IS IT ALIVE , DADDY ?
Gretchen : HEATHER .
YOU 'RE IN THE NEXT SHOT .
MIGHT AS WELL BE , DYLAN . STATE-OF-THE-ART ANIMATRONICS
ENHANCED WITH BIO-ORGANIC GRAFTING .
BULL TENDONS ,
NERVE BUNDLES FROM A LIVE DOBERMAN .
Heather : CHASE .
UH-OH .
CHUCK !
IT MUST 'VE HAVE PICKED UP A SIGNAL
FROM AN EIGHTIES WALKIE-TALKIE .
IT 'S OFF ? YES .
FUNNY , IT 'S WARM- - JUST LIKE A REAL HAND .
[ CHUCKLING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GURGLING ]
OH , GOD .
WHAT THE HELL 'S GOING ON HERE ? CUT THE EFFECTS !
Heather : CHASE !
TERRY , WHERE IS IT ?
TERRY !
CHUCK , GET OFF ME .
HEATHER !
HEATHER , WHERE IS IT ?
Terry : CHASE , WHERE THE HELL IS IT ?
DYLAN !
COME ON .
[ SCREAMING ]
WHAT THE FUCK ? !
DYLAN .
NO ! CHASE !
NO !
[ SCREAMS ]
EARTHQUAKE . COME ON .
OK .
Dylan : MOMMY !
DYLAN !
Chase : HEATHER !
AAH . DYLAN .
[ RUMBLING SUBSIDES ]
[ CAR ALARMS WAILING ]
WHAT IS THAT ?
CAR ALARMS .
[ SIGHS ]
YOU OK ?
YEAH .
YOU OK , CHIEF ?
NO .
HONEY , DO YOU HAVE A FEVER ?
JUST ANOTHER EARTHQUAKE , DYLAN .
GETTING KIND OF FUN , HUH ?
DADDY . BLOOD .
IT 'S NOTHING , GUYS .
IT 'S A SCRATCH .
REALLY .
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
PICTURE , I GUESS .
WHEN IT FELL . IT 'S NO BIG DEAL .
PUT A BANDAGE ON IT .
DON 'T WORRY ABOUT IT .
WHOO !
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ SIRENS IN THE DISTANCE ]
Newscaster : GEOLOGISTS AT CAL TECH
HAVE CONFIRMED THAT THIS MORNING 'S AFTERSHOCK ...
DO WE HAVE TO WATCH THAT ?
... 5.3 ON THE RICHTER SCALE .
Chase : THOUGHT YOU TURNED IT ON .
... TO CAUSE FURTHER COLLAPSE
OF THE ALREADY BADLY DAMAGED PARKING STRUCTURE ...
I 'LL TURN IT OFF .
Newscaster : OFFICIALS SAY THAT THIS IS NORMAL
FOLLOWING A QUAKE OF LAST WEEK 'S MAGNITUDE ,
NOW THOUGHT TO BE A MASSIVE 6.8 .
DYLAN , THIS IS BREAKFAST , NOT ARTS AND CRAFTS .
GRRR .
WHAT ?
DID YOU GET ANY SLEEP LAST NIGHT ?
MORE OR LESS .
OK , TIME TO GET DRESSED .
I 'M LATE .
YOU GOING AWAY ?
JUST FOR A FEW HOURS . JULIE WILL BE WITH YOU .
IS THERE ANYTHING OTHER THAN THE OBVIOUS
BOTHERING YOU ?
I THINK 5 EARTHQUAKES IN 3 WEEKS IS ENOUGH , SWEETIE .
HASN 'T BEEN ANOTHER PHONE CALL , HAS THERE ?
NO .
OH . GOOD SIGN .
2 FULL WEEKS WITHOUT HIM .
MAYBE HE GOT HIT BY A TRUCK .
[ SIGHS ] HE 'S CLOSER , IF ANYTHING .
IT 'S GIVING ME NIGHTMARES , CHASE .
DID YOU HAVE ONE LAST NIGHT ?
AH , IT 'S JUST THE EARTHQUAKES , HEATHER .
MAYBE .
MAYBE I SHOULDN 'T DO THIS INTERVIEW TODAY .
NO .
YOU GOTTA GET BACK ON THE HORSE SOMETIME .
LOOK , YOU HAD A NUT CASE MAKING HARASSING PHONE CALLS .
I KNOW HOW SCARY THAT 'S BEEN .
NO ... YOU DON 'T .
OK ...
I DON 'T .
BUT IT DOESN 'T MEAN THAT IT CAN 'T BE OVER .
YEAH , BUT WHAT IF IT ISN 'T OVER ?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD TELL ME YOUR DREAM .
OH , IT WAS NOTHING .
I WAS--HMMPH .
YOU AND I WERE WORKING ON THIS MOVIE- -
TOGETHER , FOR ONCE- -
AND ONE OF YOUR SPECIAL EFFECTS
WENT REALLY WRONG .
AND CHUCK AND TERRY GOT ... HURT ...
[ SNICKERS ]
AND , UH ...
WELL , YOUR FINGERS WERE CUT .
RIGHT HERE ?
OOH-HOO-HOO-HOO !
HEATHER ...
YOU WERE PROBABLY HALF AWAKE
AND SAW MY FINGERS GET NICKED WHEN THE MIRROR FELL .
DREAMS ARE LIKE THAT .
HMM .
LOOK , IF YOU DON 'T WANT ME TO GO ON THIS JOB , I WON 'T .
JUST BE CAREFUL , OK ?
I THINK I CAN SURVIVE 2 DAYS IN PALM SPRINGS
SUPPLYING SOAP BUBBLES FOR A DETERGENT COMMERCIAL .
I GUESS SO .
YOU GUESS SO ?
YEAH .
COME HERE .
MMM .
48 HOURS .
I 'LL BE BACK IN NO TIME .
I GOTTA GO .
OK .
MMM .
HEY !
I LOVE WHAT YOU 'VE DONE WITH THE PLACE .
KNOCK ' EM DEAD .
Chase : DYLAN , I GOTTA GO . TAKE CARE OF MOMMY .
Dylan : BYE .
[ RUMBLING SUBSIDES ]
TV : NANCY .
NANCY .
DYLAN , I DON 'T WANT YOU WATCHING THIS .
[ SCREAMING ]
DYLAN , WHAT 'S WRONG ? WHAT 'S WRONG ? !
WHAT 'S HAPPENING TO YOU ?
[ SCREAMING ]
[ TELEPHONE RINGING ]
[ RING ]
HELLO ?
Man : ♪ 1 , 2- -
[ RING ]
HELLO ?
Man : FREDDY 'S COMING FOR YOU !
CHASE !
[ LOCKS DOOR ]
SOMEONE 'S COMING .
WHAT ?
[ RUMBLING ]
ARE YOU OK , HONEY ?
YES .
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
HEATHER !
OH !
HEY .
IS EVERYTHING OK ?
YEAH , IT 'S JUST THESE QUAKES .
DID YOU JUST FEEL A LITTLE ONE JUST NOW ?
NO . A BIG TRUCK WENT BY
RIGHT BEFORE YOU OPENED THE DOOR .
IT 'S LIFE ON THE FAULT LINE .
HEY , TIGER . HI , JULIE .
OH !
DOES HE FEEL WARM TO YOU ?
HE HAD A FEVER THIS MORNING , I THINK .
HMM . NO , HE SEEMS OK .
ARE YOU SURE THAT 'S ALL THAT 'S WRONG ?
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
LEAVE US ALONE , YOU SON OF A BITCH !
Man : L.A. LIMOUSINE , MA 'AM .
JUST WANTED YOU TO KNOW I 'M OUT FRONT .
I 'M SORRY . CAN YOU HANG ON A MINUTE ?
[ SIGHS ]
HEATHER ...
WHAT IS IT ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
I JUST HAVE THIS WEIRD FEELING TODAY .
MOMMY ?
STAY HOME , THEN .
DYLAN ...
THIS DAMN CALLER .
HE 'S STARTED AGAIN ?
THAT SICK FUCK .
SORRY .
YOU KNOW , DYLAN DOESN 'T SEEM TO HAVE A FEVER .
IT 'S PROBABLY JUST YOUR NERVES .
NERVES ?
I JUST MEANT FROM THE SHAKER THIS MORNING .
EVERYBODY 'S BEEN FREAKED OUT
ABOUT HOW MANY WE 'VE BEEN HAVING .
AND THEN THESE PHONE CALLS .
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
DON 'T ANSWER IT .
[ RING ]
HELLO ?
Man : EXCUSE ME , MA 'AM , BUT WE ARE GOING TO BE LATE .
OK .
DYLAN , I GOTTA GO . FORGIVE ME ?
BYE .
I 'LL CALL THE COPS FOR YOU .
YOU 'VE GOT THE NUMBER ON THE FRIDGE , RIGHT ?
YOU JUST GIVE THEM THE TIME THEY CALLED ,
AND THEN THEY 'RE KEEPING THIS LIST , SUPPOSEDLY .
AND , JULIE ... I 'M REALLY SORRY .
MY NERVES ARE A LITTLE RAW THESE DAYS .
IT 'S OK .
HA HA HA ! YEAH . I GOTTA GO .
MORNING .
GOOD MORNING .
YOU PLAYED THAT GIRL .
IN THAT MOVIE .
WITH THE GUY WITH THE--FFT !
YEAH , SURE . THAT 'S YOU .
THAT 'S WHAT I LOVE ABOUT THIS JOB .
I GET TO MEET THE STARS .
I 'M HARDLY A STAR .
WHAT , ARE YOU KIDDING ?
I LOVE YOUR STUFF .
THE FIRST WAS THE BEST .
WHERE THE GIRLFRIEND 'S CUT OPEN AND DRAGGED ACROSS THE CEILING .
IT WAS AWESOME .
AND WHEN ALL THAT BLOOD COMES OUT OF YOUR BOYFRIEND 'S BED ?
I THOUGHT I 'D SHIT .
BUT THEY NEVER SHOULD HAVE KILLED OFF FREDDY .
HEATHER , LOOK , WE GOTTA GO .
CUTTING IT KIND OF CLOSE , AREN 'T YOU ?
WHAT , ARE YOU TRYING TO GET ME FIRED ?
OK , OK , OK ! WE 'RE COMING !
NO , NO , NO , NO !
SO , HEATHER ,
WE 'RE APPROACHING THE 10th ANNIVERSARY
OF THIS WHOLE NIGHTMARE ON ELM STREET THING .
I MEAN , THE ORIGINAL , 5 VERY POPULAR SEQUELS .
HOW HAS ALL THE SUCCESS AFFECTED YOU PERSONALLY ?
I DON 'T KNOW IF IT REALLY HAS , SAM .
I- - [ LAUGHS ] GOD .
WITH THE EXCEPTION OF 1 AND 3 ,
I PRETTY MUCH STAYED OUT OF IT , AND , UH ...
WELL , YOU KNOW , I 'M DOING A LOT MORE TELEVISION NOW ,
SO THOSE HOURS LET ME SPEND A LOT MORE TIME
WITH MY HUSBAND AND MY LITTLE BOY .
THAT 'S RIGHT . YOU HAVE A LITTLE BOY .
WHAT 'S HIS NAME ?
DYLAN .
WITH DYLAN , DOES THAT CHANGE YOUR FEELING ,
YOUR PERSPECTIVE ABOUT HORROR MOVIES ?
NO , NOT REALLY .
I MEAN , WOULD YOU LET HIM SEE ONE OF YOUR MOVIES ?
MY SON ? NO .
I 'M SURE PEOPLE ASK YOU THIS ALL THE TIME- -
IS THERE GOING TO BE ANOTHER SEQUEL ,
AND WHAT 'S MORE ,
IS FREDDY REALLY DEAD ?
OF COURSE HE IS . FREDDY 'S DEAD AND GONE .
AND HOW ABOUT YOUR COSTAR IN THE ORIGINAL ,
IN NIGHTMARE 1 ,
WOULD YOU TRUST HIM ALONE WITH DYLAN ?
ROBERT ? I DON 'T KNOW .
WHY DON 'T WE ASK HIM HOW HE 'D FEEL ABOUT IT ?
WE 'VE GOT A BIG SURPRISE FOR YOU , HEATHER ,
AND FOR OUR AUDIENCE .
LET 'S BRING HIM OUT .
HE IS THE BEST OF THE BAD .
LET 'S SAY HELLO TO ROBERT ENGLUND .
[ APPLAUSE ]
HA HA ! LOVE YA , BABE !
WE 'LL DO LUNCH ! HA !
I 'M ALIVE ONCE AGAIN !
FREDDY 'S BACK ! GIVE IT UP FOR YOUR UNCLE FREDDY !
HA HA HA !
JUST WHEN YOU THOUGHT IT WAS SAFE TO GET BACK INTO BED !
HA HA ! HA HA !
GIVE ME 5 !
HA HA HA HA !
I 'M BACK , AND I 'M BADDER THAN EVER !
YEAH ! YEAH !
Crowd : FREDDY ! FREDDY ! FREDDY !
HA ! YOU ARE ALL MY CHILDREN NOW !
HA HA HA HA !
I GOT TO GO , ROBERT .
UM , JUST A SECOND . I 'LL WALK YOU .
THERE YOU GO , KIDS .
Child : THANK YOU .
BYE-BYE .
YOU OK ?
YEAH , I 'M FINE .
WELL , EVERYTHING WENT GREAT , I THOUGHT .
WE REALLY GOT YOU , DIDN 'T WE ?
I DON 'T KNOW WHY YOU DIDN 'T TELL ME .
OH , COME ON . THEY LOVED THE EXPRESSION
ON YOUR FACE .
I THINK THEY 'D LIKE TO SEE US TOGETHER AGAIN .
IN WHAT , A ROMANTIC COMEDY ?
JUST BECAUSE IT 'S A LOVE STORY
DOESN 'T MEAN YOU CAN 'T HAVE A DECAPITATION OR TWO .
Man : HEATHER . THERE 'S A CALL FOR YOU .
FOR ME ?
LISTEN , I 'LL TALK TO YOU LATER .
BYE-BYE . BYE-BYE .
HELLO ?
HEATHER , IT 'S SARA RISHER OVER AT NEW LINE CINEMA .
HOW ARE YOU ?
HI , SARA . HOW ARE YOU ?
THIS IS A VOICE FROM THE PAST .
IT SURE IS .
WELL , LISTEN , HEATHER , I WON 'T TAKE BUT A MINUTE .
IT 'S JUST THAT WE HAVE SOMETHING TO PROPOSE TO YOU ,
AND I WONDER IF YOU 'D STOP BY THE OFFICES .
BOB WOULD LOVE TO TALK TO YOU .
WELL , SURE . WHEN ?
NO TIME LIKE THE PRESENT . THE CAR WILL BRING YOU OVER .
NOW ?
JUST TAKE A MINUTE .
YOU 'LL BE GLAD YOU DID , I BET . BYE .
CAN I HELP YOU ?
I 'M HERE TO SEE BOB SHAYE .
WAS BOB EXPECTING YOU ?
HEATHER . HI .
SARA . HOW ARE YOU ?
I 'M FINE . HOW ARE YOU ?
GREAT TO SEE YOU .
YOU LOOK GREAT .
THANK YOU .
BOB IS DYING TO SEE YOU .
CAN I GET YOU SOMETHING TO DRINK ?
COFFEE WOULD BE FINE .
BLACK ? BLACK 'S FINE .
KIM , COULD YOU GET US SOME COFFEE ?
SURE . THANKS .
Bob : I THINK THE GUY IS A LITTLE BIT OF A JERK ,
BUT WE WON 'T KNOW UNTIL WE 'VE READ THE SCRIPT .
ANYHOW , I 'LL GIVE YOU A CALL WHEN I- -
HEY ! LISTEN , MAN , I GOT TO GO .
SEE YOU LATER , OK ? THANKS .
CALL ME WHEN YOU GET TO MILAN ,
AND DON 'T FORGET- - RISOTTO CON TARTUFI .
IT 'S FANTASTICO !
YEAH , TAKE CARE , MAN . I 'LL TALK TO YOU LATER . BYE .
BOY , DO YOU LOOK GREAT , HEATHER .
THANKS .
HOW ARE YOU ?
GREAT . I 'M FINE .
AND I DON 'T HAVE TO ASK HOW YOU 'RE DOING .
WELL , SO FAR SO GOOD . WHICH , BY THE WAY ,
IS WHY WE ASKED YOU TO COME BY TODAY .
AH , THANKS , KIM .
SURE .
LOOK , HEATHER , LET ME CUT TO THE CHASE .
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE TO JOIN US
IN THE DEFINITIVE NIGHTMARE ?
I THOUGHT YOU KILLED FREDDY OFF .
WELL , WE DID , BUT THE FANS ,
YOU KNOW , THE FANS , GOD BLESS THEM ,
THEY 'RE CLAMORING FOR MORE .
I GUESS EVIL NEVER DIES , RIGHT ?
ANYHOW , A FEW WEEKS AGO , I GOT A CALL FROM WES ,
AND HE PITCHED ME THIS REALLY EXCITING IDEA ,
AND I STARTED THINKING ,
" WHO BETTER TO RESURRECT FREDDY THAN HIS CREATOR ? "
WELL , I THOUGHT WES STOPPED DOING HORROR MOVIES .
[ SCOFFS ] DO YOU KNOW HE ACTUALLY TOLD ME
HE HADN 'T CALLED ME IN THE LAST 10 YEARS
BECAUSE HE HADN 'T HAD ANY REALLY SCARY NIGHTMARES ?
THEY 'RE HIS INSPIRATION FOR THIS THING .
ANYHOW , HE 'S--HE 'S RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF THE SCRIPT .
WHICH MEANS HE 'S HAVING NIGHTMARES AGAIN .
WELL , HE 'S VERY EXCITED ABOUT IT .
THE NIGHTMARES ?
NO , SWEETIE , THE SCRIPT .
AND YOU SHOULD BE , TOO , BECAUSE ...
YOU 'RE THE STAR .
I DON 'T KNOW , BOB .
I 'M FLATTERED , REALLY ,
BUT I HAVE A KID NOW , AND ...
WELL , SO ?
SO I 'M NOT SURE ABOUT DOING HORROR .
OH , COME ON , HEATHER . KIDS LOVE HORROR .
THANK YOU SO MUCH , BOB .
I HAVE OTHER THINGS HAPPENING .
HEATHER , LOOK , I PROMISE YOU
WE 'LL MATCH ANY OFFER THAT 'S ON THE TABLE FOR YOU .
NO , IT 'S NOT THAT . IT 'S ...
LOOK , I HAVE A FAN .
HEATHER , YOU GOT PLENTY OF FANS .
WE 'VE BEEN DOING MARKETING RESEARCH ON YOU .
YOU ARE RATING RIGHT UP THERE .
LOOK , WE 'VE GOT CHASE
WORKING ON A PROTOTYPE FOR THE NEW GLOVE .
IT 'S REALLY- - WHAT ?
OK , I KNOW .
WE ASKED HIM TO KIND OF KEEP IT AS A SURPRISE
UNTIL YOU AND I COULD HAVE THIS CONVERSATION .
BOB ...
HOW LONG HAS WES BEEN WORKING ON THIS SCRIPT ?
I DON 'T KNOW . A COUPLE OF MONTHS . WHY ?
AND SINCE YOU 'VE BEEN THINKING OF MAKING IT ,
HAS ANYTHING FUNNY HAPPENED ?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
WELL , LIKE ... WEIRD PHONE CALLS .
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
OR NIGHTMARES .
[ RING ]
WHY DON 'T YOU ANSWER YOUR PHONE , BOB ?
THAT 'S WHAT WE GOT PEOPLE WE PAY AROUND HERE FOR .
WILL SOMEONE PICK UP THE DAMN PHONE ?
[ RING ]
THANKS A LOT .
YOU 'RE WELCOME .
[ DYLAN SCREAMING ]
DYLAN ?
WHAT THE- -
EEE !
[ SCARY VOICE ] NEVER SLEEP AGAIN .
NEVER SLEEP AGAIN .
[ SCREAMING ]
OH , WHAT IS GOING ON ?
YOU DIDN 'T LET HIM WATCH THE MOVIE ON TV , DID YOU ?
MOVIE ? HE DIDN 'T WATCH ANYTHING ON TV .
HE WAS TAKING HIS NAP , AND I HEARD HIM SCREAMING .
HONEY , ARE YOU OK ?
MM-HMM .
REX SAVED ME .
HE DID ?
[ PANTING ]
IS REX GOING TO DIE ?
NO .
REX IS NOT GOING TO DIE .
I PROMISE YOU , SWEETIE .
DO YOU KNOW WHERE THE SEWING STUFF IS
IN THE KITCHEN ?
SURE .
WE 'LL DO AN OPERATION , OK ?
COME ON .
DR. DYLAN AND DR. JULIE .
FIX HIM UP GOOD AS NEW , OK ?
Man : HEY , CHASE . YOU 'VE GOT A CALL .
IT 'S YOUR WIFE .
HEATHER .
CHASE , HI .
CHASE , YOU BETTER COME HOME .
OH , HEATHER . I 'M STUCK HERE .
NEITHER CHUCK OR TERRY CAME IN TODAY .
WHY ? WHAT 'S THE MATTER ?
CHASE , IT 'S DYLAN .
WHAT ?
[ STATIC ]
HOLD ON . THE PHONE 'S BREAKING UP .
Chase : OK . WHAT 'S GOING ON WITH DYLAN ?
HE 'S HAD SOME SORT OF A ... EPISODE .
WHAT ?
WHAT KIND OF EPISODE ?
HE WAS JUST ACTING VERY STRANGELY .
LIKE SOMEBODY WAS AFTER HIM .
IT 'S SCARY . IT SCARED ME .
HE WAS ACTING LIKE ...
LIKE WHAT ?
LIKE FREDDY .
HEATHER , HAS THERE BEEN ANOTHER PHONE CALL ?
CHASE , WHY DIDN 'T YOU TELL ME
YOU WERE WORKING ON A NEW GLOVE ?
AND WHY AREN 'T CHUCK AND TERRY AT WORK TODAY ?
FORGET THOSE CLOWNS , HEATHER . ANSWER ME .
HAS THERE BEEN ANOTHER PHONE CALL TODAY OR NOT ?
YES .
[ SIGHS ]
OK .
I 'M COMING HOME .
I 'LL BE THERE IN 3 HOURS .
[ CLICK ]
DANNY , I GOT TO GO .
WHAT 'S UP , CHASE ?
MY KID 'S SICK . I GOT TO FLY .
[ TRUCK STARTS ]
Heather : " AS SOON AS THE SUN WAS UP ,
" THE WITCH MADE GRETEL FETCH THE WOOD
" AND KINDLE A FIRE .
" WE WILL BAKE COOKIES FIRST , SHE SAID .
" I 'VE HEATED THE OVEN AND KNEADED THE DOUGH .
" CRAWL IN AND SEE IF THE FIRE IS BLAZING HIGH ENOUGH NOW .
" AND SHE PUSHED GRETEL TOWARD THE OVEN .
" THE WITCH WENT TO SHUT THE DOOR
AND BAKE HER ONCE SHE WAS INSIDE . "
DYLAN , THIS IS SO VIOLENT .
I DON 'T KNOW WHY YOU LIKE THESE STUPID OLD FAIRY TALES .
FINISH , PLEASE .
THEY 'RE GONNA GIVE YOU NIGHTMARES .
I LIKE THIS STORY .
[ SIGHS ]
" BUT GRETEL GUESSED WHAT THE WITCH WAS PLANNING .
" I DON 'T KNOW HOW TO GET IN , GRETEL SAID .
" HOW AM I TO MANAGE IT ?
" STUPID GIRL , SHOUTED THE WITCH ,
" RUSHING UP TO THE OVEN .
" THE OPENING IS BIG ENOUGH . SEE ? I CAN FIT MYSELF .
" THEN QUICKLY , GRETEL CAME BEHIND
" AND PUSHED WITH ALL HER MIGHT ,
" PLUNGING THE WICKED OLD WOMAN HEADLONG INTO THE FLAMES ,
" BANGING THE DOOR SHUT AND BOLTING IT TIGHT .
THE WITCH HOWLED ... "
THAT 'S ENOUGH .
" THE WITCH HOWLED LIKE A SCALDED CAT ,
" BUT GRETEL RAN
" AND LEFT HER THERE TO PERISH NONETHELESS .
" SHE RAN TO HER BROTHER AS FAST AS SHE COULD ,
" FLUNG OPEN THE DOOR . HANSEL ! HANSEL , SHE CRIED .
WE 'RE SAVED ! THE WITCH IS DEAD . "
TIME FOR SLEEP .
SAY HOW THEY FIND THEIR WAY BACK HOME .
TOMORROW NIGHT .
NO . TONIGHT .
IT 'S IMPORTANT .
DYLAN , YOU KNOW AS WELL AS I DO .
THEY FOLLOWED THE TRAIL OF BREADCRUMBS
BACK TO THEIR HOUSE .
AND THEN THEIR FATHER COVERED THEM WITH KISSES ,
AND THEY WERE SAFE .
THEY WERE SAFE , AND THEY COULD SLEEP .
COME ON .
WHAT IS THAT ?
REX .
COME ON .
REX KEEPS HIM DOWN THERE .
WHO ?
THE MEAN OLD MAN WITH THE CLAWS .
HE WANTS TO COME UP WHILE WE SLEEP .
I KEEP MY FEET UP HERE .
REX KEEPS HIM DOWN THERE .
HE 'S MY GUARD .
YOU SHOULD HAVE A GUARD , TOO .
DYLAN .
THERE 'S NOTHING DOWN THERE .
COME HERE .
LOOK . SEE ?
IT 'S DIFFERENT WHEN YOU 'RE GONE .
COME ON .
ON , PLEASE .
OK , SWEETIE .
NIGHT-NIGHT .
SLEEP TIGHT .
DON 'T LET THE BEDBUGS BITE .
DADDY COMING HOME ?
HE 'S ON HIS WAY .
HE CAN FOLLOW THE BREADCRUMBS , RIGHT ?
RIGHT .
IF THE BIRDS DON 'T EAT THEM FIRST .
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ BEEP ]
[ DIALING ]
[ STATIC ]
AW ...
PERFECT , PERFECT , PERFECT !
[ STATIC ON RADIO ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ DIFFERENT MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ MAN TALKING ]
[ STATIC ]
[ SHUTS OFF RADIO ]
AHH .
COME ON , COME ON , COME ON ,
COME ON , COME ON , COME ON , COME ON .
♪ THAT 'S ME IN THE CORNER
[ HUMMING ]
♪ THAT 'S ME IN THE SPOT
♪ LIGHT
♪ LOSIN ' MY
♪ RELIGION
[ SCREAMING ]
Dylan : MOMMY 'S SCARED ?
DYLAN .
MOMMY 'S FINE .
IT WAS JUST A BAD DREAM .
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT OF BED ?
REX WOKE ME UP .
HE WAS FIGHTING .
DYLAN , GO BACK TO SLEEP , HONEY .
I 'M NOT SLEEPY .
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
Man : HELLO ?
POLICE , MA 'AM . WILL YOU OPEN THE DOOR ?
HEATHER LANGENKAMP ?
YES ?
IS CHASE PORTER YOUR HUSBAND ?
YES .
I 'M AFRAID THERE WAS AN ACCIDENT .
IT APPEARS HE FELL ASLEEP WHILE DRIVING , MA 'AM .
IS HE ... I MEAN ...
IS HE HURT ?
I 'M AFRAID IT 'S WORSE THAN THAT , MA 'AM .
IS HE DEAD ?
[ STAMMERS ] YES , MA 'AM .
OHH .
ARE YOU SURE IT 'S HIM ?
WE HAVE HIS EFFECTS .
YOU CAN CONFIRM FROM THAT .
I WANT TO SEE HIS BODY .
NO , YOU DON 'T , MA 'AM . IT 'S NOT NECESSARY .
I WANT TO SEE IT FOR MYSELF .
[ ELEVATOR RINGS ]
[ WOMAN CRYING HYSTERICALLY ]
[ ELECTRIC WHIRRING ]
Man : CAN YOU HAND ME THAT ?
Second man : SURE .
[ CLEARS THROAT ] EXCUSE ME .
COULD I HELP YOU ?
PORTER . [ WHIRRING STOPS ]
CHASE PORTER .
IT 'S--IT 'S BACK HERE .
[ WHIRRING RESUMES ]
YOU SAID CHASE ?
MM-HMM .
I 'M SORRY .
JUST SIGN HERE AT THE BOTTOM .
THAT 'S ALL WE NEED .
I 'D LIKE TO SEE ONCE AGAIN .
I 'M SORRY ?
COULD YOU LIFT THE SHEET AGAIN , PLEASE ?
MORE , PLEASE .
WHAT IS THAT ?
IT WAS A BAD WRECK , MA 'AM .
THE HEAD 'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT
FOR THE FUNERAL AND ALL , BUT- -
HEY , LADY . YOU OK ?
YOU SURE ?
MM-HMM . YES .
[ SOBBING ]
OH , GOD . WHAT DID THAT ?
WELL , THEY SAID THE TRUCK WAS TORE UP SOMETHING AWFUL ,
SO YOU CAN IMAGINE HIM NOT BEING IN ...
WELL , EXACTLY TOP SHAPE .
IT LOOKS LIKE ...
HE WAS CLAWED .
YEAH .
WELL , THAT 'S WHY WE DON 'T LIFT THE SHEET
PAST THE FACE , MA 'AM .
SOMETIMES IT 'S WHAT WE DON 'T SEE
THAT GETS US THROUGH THE NIGHT .
SO , UM ... IF YOU 'LL JUST SIGN ...
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ GEARS SQUEAKING ]
Priest : GOD IS OUR HOPE AND STRENGTH ,
A VERY PRESENT HELP IN TROUBLE .
THEREFORE , WE WILL NOT FEAR ,
THOUGH THE EARTH BE MOVED
AND THOUGH THE HILLS BE CARRIED
INTO THE MIDST OF THE SEA ,
THOUGH THE WATERS THEREOF RAGE AND SWELL
AND THOUGH THE MOUNTAINS SHAKE
AT THE TEMPEST OF THE SAME .
[ STATUE SHATTERS ]
[ EERIE WHISPERING ]
JULIE , WHERE 'S DYLAN ?
I--I DON 'T KNOW .
[ EERIE WHISPERING ]
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
AAH ! MOMMY !
DYLAN !
MOMMY ! DYLAN !
DYLAN , GRAB MOMMY 'S HAND . GRAB IT !
OH , MY GOD !
HURRY !
OH , NO . AAH ! AAH ! AAH !
LET GO OF ME !
NO !
STAY WITH ME .
CH-CHASE ! NO !
STAY WITH ME , HEATHER .
NO !
WHERE 'S DYLAN ? WHERE 'S DYLAN ?
HE 'S ALL RIGHT .
HE 'S ALL RIGHT . HE 'S RIGHT HERE .
[ HEATHER PANTING ]
AAH , WHAT HAPPENED ?
IT WAS AN EARTHQUAKE .
YOU GOT KNOCKED OFF YOUR FEET .
YOU GOT A PRETTY GOOD BUMP , ACTUALLY .
Priest : MAY HE REST IN PEACE , CHILDREN .
AND MAY YOU ALL GET HOME SAFELY .
AMEN . AMEN . AMEN .
[ CREAKING ]
[ SIREN ]
IF THERE 'S ANYTHING I CAN DO , HEATHER ...
ANYTHING .
THANK YOU , ROBERT .
[ BIRD CAWING ]
[ NIGHTMARE ON ELM STREET PLAYING ON TV ]
SWEETIE .
Heather on TV : TINA ?
[ MUTTERING ]
[ WHISPERING ] Dylan .
TINA ?
HEY .
WHO ARE YOU ?
[ GLOVE CLANGING ]
[ FREDDY LAUGHING ON TV ]
DYLAN .
BABY , WAKE UP .
AAH !
HONEY . DYLAN .
DYLAN , GET OVER HERE ! HONEY ! HONEY !
SHH SHH SHH SHH .
COME ON .
OK , SUGAR , WE 'RE GONNA GO BACK TO BED NOW .
NO , MOMMY , I CAN 'T SLEEP THERE .
HONEY , YOU HAVE TO SLEEP .
♪ 1 , 2 , FREDDY 'S COMING FOR YOU ♪
WHERE DID YOU HEAR THAT ?
DID YOU HEAR THAT ON THAT MOVIE ?
DID YOU ANSWER THE PHONE ?
DYLAN , WHERE DID YOU HEAR THAT SONG ?
IN MY BED .
IN YOUR BED ?
UNDER MY COVERS .
KIDS SINGING .
WAY DOWN THERE WITH THE MAN ,
THE MEAN MAN .
WHAT IS THAT MAN DOING ?
TRYING TO GET UP .
TRYING TO GET UP INTO OUR WORLD .
[ GASPS ] DYLAN !
[ WATER RUNNING ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
WHERE 'S DADDY NOW ?
DADDY 'S IN HEAVEN .
HE 'S WITH GOD NOW .
DO YOU HAVE TO ...
DIE TO SEE GOD ?
I DON 'T THINK SO .
I THINK YOU HAVE TO PRAY .
AND REACH OUT .
WHY DOES GOD LET THERE BE BAD THINGS ?
I HONESTLY DON 'T KNOW , HONEY .
PLEASE TRY TO GET SOME SLEEP .
CAN YOU COME WITH ME IN MY DREAMS ?
I THINK THAT ONLY HAPPENS IN THE MOVIES .
BUT I 'LL ALWAYS , ALWAYS ...
BE RIGHT HERE WHEN YOU GET BACK .
AND I 'LL MAKE SURE
THAT NOBODY GETS YOUR TOES .
UH-HUH .
Heather : I KNOW HIS BEHAVIOR IS BIZARRE ...
BUT HE 'S USUALLY SO NORMAL AND WELL ADJUSTED , JOHN ,
I JUST CAN 'T BELIEVE IT 'S HIM
AND NOT SOMETHING OUTSIDE INFLUENCING HIM .
OR IS THAT HOW DENIAL WORKS ?
WELL , IT IS DENIAL .
I DON 'T THINK THAT 'S THE CASE HERE .
LOOK , IF YOU 'RE REALLY WORRIED ABOUT DYLAN ,
HAVE A DOCTOR CHECK HIM OUT .
YOU 'LL SEE . EVERYTHING 'S FINE .
YOU 'RE NOT JUST SAYING THAT
TO HELP A CRAZY FRIEND COPE , ARE YOU ?
[ SIGHS ]
EVERYTHING ABOUT DYLAN 'S BEHAVIOR
IS UNDERSTANDABLE
FOR A KID WHO JUST LOST HIS FATHER .
HOW DOES A CHILD PROCESS A THING LIKE THAT ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
[ BICYCLE BELL RINGS ]
I 'VE NOT BEEN ABLE
TO PROCESS IT VERY WELL MYSELF .
AND YOU 'RE NOT CRAZY , BY THE WAY .
SEEING FREDDY IN THAT GRAVE FEELS PRETTY CRAZY
AND THEN JUMPING IN- -
YOU DIDN 'T JUMP IN .
THAT 'S MY MEMORY .
IT SEEMED ABSOLUTELY REAL .
" SEEMED , " NOT " WAS . "
IT 'S ...
IT 'S IN MY FAMILY , YOU KNOW .
WHAT IS ?
A VERY CLOSE RELATIVE DIED IN AN INSTITUTION .
REALLY ? WELL , IF HAVING A SCREWY FAMILY
MADE A PERSON CRAZY ,
THE WHOLE WORLD WOULD BE ONE BIG LOONY BIN .
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU HAVE A CRAZED FAN AFTER YOU .
THAT 'S WHAT 'S MAKING YOU CRAZY .
AND PROBABLY DYLAN , TOO .
I NEVER MENTIONED THAT TO HIM .
KIDS KNOW .
KIDS KNOW WHEN SOMETHING 'S BUGGING THE PARENT .
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHO THIS IS CALLING ?
FREDDY , FOR ALL I KNOW .
COME ON .
HE 'S A MAN .
OR A BOY WITH A DEEP , YOU KNOW ...
FREDDY VOICE .
6 WEEKS OF THIS ,
AND YOU 'RE SURPRISED YOU GOT FREDDY IN YOUR DREAMS ?
HELL , SONNY BONO , AFTER A WHILE ,
BEGAN SEEING HIS STALKER EVERYWHERE ,
EVEN AT MASS .
REALLY ?
AND HOW MANY TIMES DID LETTERMAN CALL THE COPS ,
THINKING THAT WOMAN WAS DOWN IN THE KITCHEN AGAIN ?
YEAH .
REALLY GETS UNDER YOUR SKIN IF YOU ...
IF YOU LET IT .
YOU REALLY THINK DYLAN 'S OK ?
DYLAN 'S FINE .
YOU 'RE FINE .
YOU 'RE HURTING , BUT YOU 'RE FINE ,
AND YOU 'RE DEFINITELY NOT CRAZY .
MY WORST FEAR- -
THAT WHATEVER MADNESS IS IN MY FAMILY
I HAVE ...
AND I 'VE PASSED IT ONTO DYLAN .
Heather : DYLAN !
HEATHER ! DYLAN !
MAKE SURE HE 'S OK , JOHN .
YEAH . ARE YOU ALL RIGHT ?
DYLAN ! OH , MY GOD .
ARE YOU OK ? HUH ?
ARE YOU SURE ? DOES ANYTHING HURT ?
DYLAN , ARE YOU ALL RIGHT ?
HONEY .
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT ? ARE YOU SURE ?
GOD WOULDN 'T TAKE ME .
OH , MY GOD . OH , HONEY .
John : IT 'S UNBELIEVABLE .
[ CAR DRIVES BY ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
[ RING ]
[ BEEP ]
YEAH ?
ROBERT .
HEATHER , YOU DOING ALL RIGHT ?
HANGING IN THERE .
YOU KNOW THE GUY THAT WAS CALLING ME ALL THE TIME ?
HE STARTED AGAIN ,
AND HE 'S PUTTING STUFF IN MY MAIL AGAIN .
OH , LISTEN , THE S.O.B.
PROBABLY READ ABOUT THE FUNERAL
IN THE PAPERS OR SOMETHING .
SICK MOTHER .
THAT 'S THE LAST THING YOU NEED RIGHT NOW ,
I 'M SURE .
ACTUALLY , IT 'S BEEN GIVING ME FREDDY NIGHTMARES .
WAIT A SECOND . NOW , LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT .
YOU 'RE HAVING NIGHTMARES ABOUT FREDDY ?
AS IN ME ?
NO . IT ISN 'T YOU .
HE 'S SCARIER .
HE 'S ...
DARKER ?
MORE EVIL ?
YEAH .
HOW DID YOU KNOW ?
CALL IT A GUESS .
PRETTY DAMN GOOD GUESS .
ANYWAY WHAT I WAS CALLING ABOUT WAS ,
HAVE YOU SEEN ANY OF THE SCRIPT BY ANY CHANCE ?
NO . WES WON 'T SHOW IT UNTIL HE 'S FINISHED .
AT LEAST THAT 'S WHAT HE TOLD ME .
WELL , WHEN IS IT GONNA BE DONE ?
[ LAUGHING ] THE WAY HE 'S WRITING ,
WHO KNOWS ?
IT 'S SO WEIRD .
I ASKED HIM HOW FAR HE WAS AT THE FUNERAL .
WHAT DID HE SAY ? OH , YEAH .
" AS FAR AS DYLAN TRYING TO REACH GOD . "
WHATEVER THAT MEANS .
WEIRD , HUH ?
PUTTING YOUR KID IN THE SCRIPT .
ROBERT ...
HAVE YOU BEEN HAVING NIGHTMARES ?
[ BIRD CAWING ]
LOOK , WE NEED TO TALK , BUT NOT OVER THE PHONE .
CAN I COME OVER ?
UM , ACTUALLY , HEATHER , UH ...
TODAY 'S NO GOOD . THERE 'S , UM ...
THERE 'S SOMETHING I HAVE TO FINISH .
TOMORROW MAYBE , HUH ?
OK , TOMORROW . BUT EARLY IN THE MORNING .
AND MEANWHILE , ROBERT , TAKE CARE , OK ?
YEAH . SURE .
[ BEEP ]
[ CREAKING ]
[ EERIE WHISPERING ]
[ RUSTLING ]
AAH !
[ PANTING ]
DAMN IT !
UHH ! UHH !
Dylan : ♪ 1 , 2 , FREDDY 'S COMING FOR YOU ♪
DYLAN ?
♪ 3 , 4 , BETTER LOCK YOUR DOOR ♪
♪ 5 , 6 , GRAB YOUR CRUCIFIX ♪
♪ 7 , 8 , BETTER STAY UP LATE ♪
DYLAN , DON 'T SING THAT SONG .
♪ 9 , 10
♪ NEVER SLEEP ... AGAIN !
DYLAN !
STOP IT !
NO ! DON 'T !
[ OBJECT SHATTERS ]
Dylan : ♪ NEVER SLEEP AGAIN
♪ NEVER SLEEP AGAIN
DYLAN .
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
YES ?
[ FREDDY LAUGHS ] I TOUCHED HIM .
AAH ! FREDDY !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SIREN ]
ANY HISTORY OF EPILEPSY IN YOUR FAMILY ?
NO .
DIABETES ?
WAS THERE A TRIGGER EVENT ,
TRAUMA , SHOCK ?
YOU HAVEN 'T SHOWN HIM
ANY OF THE FILMS YOU 'VE MADE , HAVE YOU ?
THE HORROR STUFF ?
HIS FATHER JUST PASSED AWAY .
I 'M SORRY .
BUT I 'M CONVINCED THOSE FILMS CAN TIP ...
AN UNSTABLE CHILD OVER THE EDGE .
UNSTABLE ?
DYLAN 'S NOT UNSTABLE .
HE 'S JUST UPSET .
WELL , WE 'LL RUN A BATTERY OF TESTS ,
AND WE 'LL KNOW IN A FEW DAYS .
DOES HE HAVE TO STAY OVERNIGHT ?
ABSOLUTELY .
Woman on P.A. : DR. DEGRASI ...
ANYTHING MORE HAPPEN WE NEED TO KNOW ABOUT ?
LIKE WHAT ?
SOMETIMES WHAT A CHILD SAYS
OR FANTASIZES
WILL GIVE A CLUE TO WHAT AILS HIM .
DID HE SAY ANYTHING WHILE HE WAS STILL LUCID ?
NO .
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
[ RING ]
Woman on P.A. : DR. EINHORN , LINE 237 .
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE ?
TOO SOON TO KNOW FOR SURE .
THE EARLY SYMPTOMS POINT TO CHILDHOOD SCHIZOPHRENIA .
DYLAN , CAN YOU HEAR ME ?
DYLAN , YOU HAVE TO FIGHT IT ,
WHATEVER IT IS THAT 'S AFTER YOU ,
AND YOU GOT TO COME BACK TO ME .
YOU CAN 'T MAKE IT ALONE . DO YOU HEAR ?
IF YOU CAN HEAR ME , THEN YOU CAN TELL ME
WHAT YOU NEED TO FEEL SAFE .
REX ? IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT ?
WELL , REX IS AT HOME ,
AND THAT 'S WHERE YOU SHOULD BE .
BUT YOU GOT TO GET BETTER
BEFORE THEY 'LL LET YOU COME HOME .
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ?
HOME .
HOME . HOME , THAT 'S RIGHT .
THAT 'S WHERE I WANT YOU , SWEETIE .
AND , YOU KNOW , WE 'RE NOT THAT FAR AWAY .
LOOK . LOOK RIGHT OUT THERE .
PAST THE FREEWAY IS OUR HOME .
BUT TO GET THERE ,
YOU HAVE TO COME OUT FROM WHERE YOU ARE
SO THAT THEY 'LL LET YOU COME HOME TO REX .
AND TO ME .
TIME FOR YOUR MEDICINE , COWBOY .
HERE YOU GO .
WHAT IS THAT ?
SOMETHING TO HELP HIM SLEEP .
OK .
THERE YOU GO .
IT LOOKS GOOD .
GOOD . GOOD . ATTABOY .
COME ON , NOW LIE DOWN AND TAKE A LITTLE NAP .
YOU SHOULD GET SOME REST , TOO .
HE 'S GOING TO BE FINE . WE 'RE GONNA DO SOME TESTS ,
AND THEN YOU CAN COME BACK LATER .
CAN YOU GET THAT OTHER SIDE , PLEASE ?
I GRABBED HIS THINGS .
THESE ARE HIS FAVORITE PAJAMAS HERE .
UM ... HONEY , I 'VE GOT TO GO .
I LOVE YOU , DYLAN .
REMEMBER WHAT I SAID .
WE 'LL TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING .
GOOD-BYE .
[ BREATHING ]
[ HORN HONKS ]
Man : WAKE UP , LADY !
DON 'T LOSE IT NOW !
Woman on radio : SEISMOLOGISTS AT CAL TECH
HAVE COUNTED OVER 300 TEMBLORS SO FAR .
THOUGH MOST WERE TOO FAINT FOR US TO FEEL ,
7 HAVE SHAKEN OUR COMMUNITY IN THE LAST FEW WEEKS ,
AND NOW SCIENTISTS ARE SPECULATING
THERE MIGHT BE AN UNKNOWN FAULT
RUNNING BENEATH LOS ANGELES ,
A FAULT THAT COULD- -
[ SHUTS OFF RADIO ]
[ BEEP ]
[ DIALING ]
[ LINE RINGS ]
Robert : HI . YOU 'VE REACHED THE ENGLUND RESIDENCE .
WE 'RE OUT OF TOWN .
YOU CAN LEAVE A MESSAGE IF YOU WISH , BUT , UH ...
WE 'LL BE GONE FOR SOME TIME .
I WISH I COULD TELL YOU WHERE THE SCRIPT WAS GOING .
THE FACT IS I DON 'T KNOW .
NO , I ... I DREAM A SCENE AT NIGHT ,
I WRITE IT DOWN IN THE MORNING .
BEYOND THAT , YOUR GUESS IS AS GOOD AS MINE WHERE IT 'S GOING .
WELL , AT LEAST TELL ME WHAT IT 'S ABOUT SO FAR .
COFFEE .
THANKS .
I CAN TELL YOU
WHAT THE NIGHTMARE 'S ABOUT SO FAR .
IT 'S ABOUT THIS ENTITY- -
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO CALL IT .
IT 'S OLD . IT 'S VERY OLD .
[ SIGHS ] IT 'S EXISTED IN DIFFERENT FORMS
IN DIFFERENT TIMES .
ABOUT THE ONLY THING THAT STAYS THE SAME
IS WHAT IT LIVES FOR , REALLY .
WHAT IS THAT ?
OH , THE MURDER OF INNOCENTS .
THIS IS STILL A SCRIPT WE 'RE TALKING ABOUT ,
RIGHT , WES ?
YEAH , WELL , I SORT OF THINK OF IT
AS A NIGHTMARE IN PROGRESS .
WELL , IN THIS NIGHTMARE IN PROGRESS THEN ,
DOES THIS THING HAVE ANY WEAKNESSES ?
YEAH , WELL , IT CAN BE CAPTURED SOMETIMES .
CAPTURED ? HOW ?
BY STORYTELLERS , OF ALL THINGS .
I MEAN , EVERY SO OFTEN ,
THEY IMAGINE A STORY GOOD ENOUGH
TO SORT OF CATCH ITS ESSENCE .
AND THEN , FOR A WHILE
IT 'S HELD PRISONER IN THE STORY .
LIKE THE GENIE IN THE BOTTLE .
EXACTLY . EXACTLY .
BUT THE PROBLEM COMES WHEN THE STORY DIES .
AND THAT CAN HAPPEN IN A LOT OF WAYS .
IT CAN GET TOO FAMILIAR TO PEOPLE
OR SOMEBODY WATERS IT DOWN
TO MAKE IT AN EASIER SELL , YOU KNOW , OR ...
MAYBE IT 'S JUST SO UPSETTING TO SOCIETY
THAT IT 'S BANNED OUTRIGHT .
HOWEVER IT HAPPENS , WHEN THE STORY DIES ,
THE EVIL IS SET FREE .
YOU 'RE SAYING FREDDY
IS THIS ANCIENT THING ?
RIGHT . THE CURRENT VERSION .
AND FOR 10 YEARS ,
HE 'S BEEN HELD CAPTIVE PRETTY MUCH AS FREDDY
IN THE NIGHTMARE ON ELM STREET SERIES ,
BUT ...
NOW THAT THE FILMS HAVE ENDED ,
THE GENIE 'S OUT OF THE BOTTLE .
THAT 'S WHAT THE NIGHTMARES ARE TELLING ME .
THAT 'S WHAT I 'M WRITING .
WELL , IF FREDDY IS LOOSE IN YOUR SCRIPT ,
WHERE 'S HE GONNA GO ?
ANOTHER AGE ? ANOTHER FORM ?
NO , THAT 'S NOT WHAT THE DREAMS HAVE HIM DOING .
WHAT IS HE DOING ?
HE 'S SORT OF GOTTEN USED TO BEING FREDDY NOW ,
AND HE LIKES OUR TIME AND SPACE ,
SO HE 'S DECIDED TO CROSS OVER
OUT OF FILMS INTO OUR REALITY .
ISN 'T THERE SOMEBODY WHO CAN STOP HIM ?
ACTUALLY THERE IS A PERSON IN THE DREAM ,
SORT OF A GATEKEEPER , SO TO SPEAK .
SOMEBODY THAT FREDDY HAS TO GET BY
BEFORE HE CAN COME THROUGH INTO OUR WORLD .
THAT PERSON 'S YOU , HEATHER .
IT 'S ME ?
YEAH .
WHY ME ?
WELL , DRAMATICALLY SPEAKING ,
IT MAKES PERFECT SENSE .
YOU PLAYED NANCY , AFTER ALL ,
AND YOU WERE THE FIRST TO HUMILIATE HIM ,
DEFEAT HIM .
THAT WAS NANCY , WES . THAT 'S NOT ME .
YEAH , BUT IT WAS YOU THAT GAVE NANCY HER STRENGTH .
SO IN ORDER TO GET OUT ,
HE 'S GOT TO COME THROUGH YOU .
AND IT 'S INEVITABLE
THAT HE 'S GONNA TRY TO DO THAT
AT YOUR MOST VULNERABLE POINTS .
OH , MY GOD , WES .
DID YOU KNOW ?
IT--IT WAS A SCRIPT . IT WAS A DREAM .
I DIDN 'T- - I DIDN 'T KNOW .
YOU KNOW DAMN WELL IT 'S MORE THAN THAT NOW .
WES .
WES ?
HOW CAN WE STOP HIM ?
I THINK THE ONLY WAY TO STOP HIM
IS TO MAKE ANOTHER MOVIE .
NOW I SWEAR TO YOU ,
I 'M GONNA STAY BY THIS COMPUTER
AND KEEP WRITING UNTIL I FINISH THE SCRIPT , BUT ...
WHEN THAT TIME COMES ,
YOU 'RE GONNA HAVE TO MAKE A CHOICE .
CHOICE ?
WHAT KIND OF CHOICE ?
WHETHER OR NOT YOU 'RE WILLING TO PLAY NANCY
ONE LAST TIME .
" MANY OF THE SYMPTOMS OF CHILDHOOD SCHIZOPHRENIA
" ARE DUPLICATED IN CHILDREN
SUFFERING FROM SLEEP DEPRIVATION . "
" SLEEP DEPRIVATION CAN PRODUCE TRANCE-LIKE STATES ,
" MECHANICAL BEHAVIOR .
THE CHILD MIGHT ... "
REX WOKE ME UP .
HE WAS FIGHTING THE MEAN OLD MAN WITH THE CLAWS .
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHO THIS IS CALLING ?
FREDDY , FOR ALL I KNOW .
AS IN ME ?
NO , IT ISN 'T YOU . HE 'S SCARIER .
DARKER , MORE EVIL ?
HOW DID YOU KNOW ?
HE 'S DECIDED TO CROSS OVER ,
OUT OF FILMS , INTO OUR REALITY .
NEVER SLEEP AGAIN .
[ STATIC HISSING ]
THE WORLD OF HORROR FILMS
SUFFERED ITS OWN TERROR TODAY ,
AS 2 OF HOLLYWOOD 'S BEST KNOWN SPECIAL-EFFECTS TECHNICIANS
WERE FOUND DEAD
IN A VACANT FIELD .
TERRANCE FEINSTEIN AND CHARLES WILSON ,
2 SPECIAL-EFFECTS ARTISTS
REPUTEDLY WORKING ON A TOP-SECRET PROJECT
FOR THE MAKERS OF THE FREDDY KRUEGER FILMS
WERE FOUND BRUTALLY SLASHED TO DEATH EARLY THIS MORNING .
[ RUMBLING ]
FREDDY 'S GLOVE WAS MISSING ,
AND POLICE ARE SPECULATING THE MURDERS WERE THE RESULT
OF A BOTCHED THEFT , WHICH APPARENTLY TOOK PLACE
2 DAYS AGO . AT THIS POINT , THE MURDER WEAPON HAS NOT- -
AAH !
[ RUMBLING STOPS ]
[ CREAK ]
OH , GOD .
MISS ME ?
AAH !
NANCY .
[ CREAK ]
OW !
OHH !
OH , DYLAN , DYLAN .
Nurse : THERE ARE NO VISITING HOURS THIS LATE .
YOU MUST UNDERSTAND .
Julie : NO , I DON 'T UNDERSTAND .
I TOLD YOU I 'M HIS BABY-SITTER .
I 'M A CLOSE FRIEND OF THE FAMILY , DAMN IT .
I JUST NEED TO SEE HIM FOR A MINUTE .
60 SECONDS . COME ON .
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND .
JULIE ?
HEATHER .
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
I HAD THIS REALLY TERRIBLE DREAM ABOUT DYLAN .
I HAD TO COME AND SEE HIM .
YOU MUST THINK I 'M CRAZY .
NO , I DON 'T .
IS HE ALL RIGHT ?
I DON 'T KNOW . THEY WOULDN 'T LET ME IN .
MISS LANGENKAMP .
I 'M AFRAID THERE ARE
NO EVENING VISITING HOURS IN INTENSIVE CARE .
IS HE ALL RIGHT ?
DYLAN ? HE 'S HOLDING WELL .
EARLIER HE HAD SOME PROBLEMS .
HE 'S IN AN OXYGEN TENT NOW .
OH , MY GOD . HEATHER .
SEEMS WE 'VE HAD AN ACCIDENT ,
MISS LANGENKAMP . MAY I ?
THOSE ARE NASTY CUTS .
HOW DID YOU GET THEM ?
IT HAPPENED IN THE EARTHQUAKE .
I FELL .
I NEED TO SEE DYLAN .
IN A MOMENT . FIRST LET 'S SEE ABOUT YOU .
IF THESE HAD BEEN A FEW INCHES
NEARER THE WRIST ...
WHAT DID YOU SAY YOU CUT YOURSELF ON ?
IT WAS THE EARTHQUAKE . IT WAS DARK . I HAVE NO IDEA .
BUT THESE LOOK QUITE FRESH .
THEY ARE . IT HAPPENED IN TONIGHT 'S EARTHQUAKE .
IT HAPPENED JUST 15 MINUTES AGO .
YOU MUST HAVE FELT IT .
GUESS WE LUCKED OUT OVER HERE .
YOUR SON ...
IS APPARENTLY TERRIFIED OF A MAN- -
SOMEONE HE THINKS
IS GOING TO COME OUT OF HIS BED .
ONE OF THE NURSES HEARD HIM TALKING TO HIMSELF .
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHO THAT MAN IS ,
MISS LANGENKAMP ?
I FORGOT TO BRING HIS DINOSAUR REX .
HE KEEPS FREDDY FROM COMING UP OUT OF HIS- -
BED .
THE MAN FROM YOUR FILMS ?
FREDDY KRUEGER ?
WITH THE CLAWS ?
IS THAT WHO HE 'S AFRAID OF ?
YOU HAVE LET YOUR CHILD SEE YOUR FILMS , HAVEN 'T YOU ?
EVERY KID KNOWS WHO FREDDY IS .
HE 'S LIKE SANTA CLAUS ...
OR KING KONG OR ...
YES .
WELL , INTERESTING TALKING WITH YOU , MISS LANGENKAMP .
I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND .
MY CONCERNS ARE SIMPLY FOR THE WELFARE OF YOUR SON .
[ HEART MONITOR BEEPING ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
HOW 'S HE DOING ?
[ BEEP ]
DYLAN .
HONEY .
YOU SHOULDN 'T DO THAT .
TOO LATE .
I 'M ALMOST THERE , HEATHER .
ALMOST THERE .
DADDY !
DYLAN !
DOCTOR !
KEEP HER RIGHT THERE .
Nurse : WE CAN 'T HOLD HIM MUCH LONGER , DOCTOR .
GET THE FULL ANESTHETIC , STAT .
WE DON 'T HAVE THAT HERE , DOCTOR .
NO ANESTHETIC , YOU SAY ?
SCREW IT , THEN . I 'M GOING IN .
LITTLE BOOGER 'S FULL OF SOMETHING I DON 'T LIKE .
LET 'S GET HIM OPEN , GOOD AND PROPER .
CUT THIS EVIL OUT OF HIM .
HA !
NO , NO !
GLORIA !
HE 'S GOT MY BABY ! WHO ?
FREDDY !
WHO ? FREDDY KRUEGER OR SOMETHING ?
WHAT THE HELL 'S GOING ON ?
MY BABY !
FREDDY 'S GOT MY BABY . HE 'S GOT MY DYLAN .
MISS LANGENKAMP !
I SUGGEST YOU GO HOME AND GET SOME REST .
YOUR SON IS FINE .
HE 'S DOWNSTAIRS FOR FURTHER TESTING .
BUT HE WAS JUST HERE .
HE WAS HERE , YOU FELL ASLEEP ,
WE TOOK HIM .
YOU LOOKED SO EXHAUSTED ,
FRANKLY , WE DIDN 'T WANT TO WAKE YOU .
BESIDES , THE YOUNG WOMAN JULIE IS WITH HIM .
THAT 'S HIS BABY-SITTER , RIGHT ?
BELIEVE ME . EVERYTHING IS FINE .
EVERYTHING 'S NOT FINE .
DAMN !
CALL SECURITY .
Woman on P.A. : SECURITY , CODE YELLOW .
PEDIATRIC TESTING .
SECURITY , CODE YELLOW . PEDIATRIC TESTING .
MA 'AM . THIS IS A RESTRICTED AREA .
DO YOU HAVE A PASS ?
SCREW YOUR PASS .
IT 'S ALL RIGHT . MISS LANGENKAMP .
WHERE IS HE ?
JUST STAY CALM .
TELL US HOW HER LITTLE BOY 'S DOING .
HE 'S FINE , ACTUALLY .
HE JUST CAME AROUND ABOUT 10 MINUTES AGO .
HE SEEMS TO BE SUFFERING
FROM ACUTE SLEEP DEPRIVATION .
[ WHISPERING ] I don 't think
she ever lets him get a night 's sleep .
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING ?
WHERE IS HE ?
HEATHER .
I 'VE GOT SOMEONE HERE WHO WANTS TO SEE YOU .
Heather : DYLAN .
OH , DYLAN , OH .
ARE YOU OK , CHAMP ?
CAN WE GO GET REX NOW ?
THE BAD MAN 'S GETTING AWFUL CLOSE .
I KNOW HE IS .
WE 'RE GONNA GO GET REX RIGHT NOW .
I 'M AFRAID DYLAN SHOULD STAY HERE UNTIL WE KNOW
WHAT 'S CAUSING THESE EPISODES , MISS LANGENKAMP .
I 'M SURE YOU UNDERSTAND .
GOOD .
LOOK , I 'LL TELL YOU WHAT .
I 'M GONNA GO HOME AND GET REX FOR YOU RIGHT NOW .
YOU KNOW THAT HOME ISN 'T FAR FROM HERE , RIGHT ?
RIGHT ACROSS THE FREEWAY .
THAT 'S RIGHT .
SO I WON 'T BE GONE LONG ,
AND JULIE , SHE 'S GONNA STAY RIGHT HERE WITH YOU .
YEAH , YOU BET .
HURRY UP , PLEASE .
I 'M SLEEPY .
I PROMISE . CROSS MY HEART .
BUT , DYLAN ,
UNTIL MOMMY GETS BACK ,
WHATEVER YOU DO ,
DON 'T FALL ASLEEP .
JULIE , DON 'T LET HIM OUT OF YOUR SIGHT .
WHAT 'S GOING ON HERE ?
YOUR HAIR 'S TURNING GRAY .
JULIE , KEEP HIM AWAKE .
UNDERSTAND ?
EXCUSE ME , MISS .
WOULD YOU COME WITH US FOR A SECOND ?
WHAT ? HEY !
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU THINK YOU 'RE DOING ?
GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME !
[ WHISPERING ]
DO YOU MIND ? WHAT THE HELL IS THIS ?
JUST A QUICK WORD , MISS LANGENKAMP ,
FOR DYLAN 'S SAKE .
WELL , WE 'VE HAD AN EXCITING DAY ,
HAVEN 'T WE , MISS LANGENKAMP ?
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
THIS ONE ?
RIGHT THERE .
1 , 2 , 3 . 1 , 2 , 3 .
YOU WON .
WOULD YOU MIND STEPPING OUTSIDE FOR JUST ONE MOMENT , MISS ?
AS A MATTER OF FACT , I WOULD .
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
IT 'S JUST A LITTLE SHOT TO SEE THAT HE GETS SOME SLEEP .
NO . HIS MOTHER SPECIFICALLY SAID- -
I SAID NO .
DO IT .
OW !
ALL DONE .
HE 'LL BE ASLEEP IN NO TIME .
WOULD YOU MIND LETTING GO OF MY ARM ?
YOU BITCH !
HEY , YOU CAN 'T DO THAT !
WELL , I KNOW WHAT 'S IN THAT ONE .
SO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT 'S IN THIS ONE ?
OR WHAT 'S GONNA HAPPEN TO YOU
WHEN I STICK YOU WITH IT ?
AND I WILL .
AAH !
OH , NO , NO , DYLAN .
I WANT YOU TO STAY AWAKE , OK ?
I WANT YOU TO KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN FOR ME , OK ?
MISS LANGENKAMP .
HAS THERE BEEN ANY USE
OF RECREATIONAL DRUGS IN YOUR FAMILY ?
WHAT ?
OR ANY HISTORY OF MENTAL DISTURBANCE ?
WHAT ARE YOU ASKING ?
PLEASE , DON 'T TAKE IT WRONG .
IF THERE WAS , THERE 'S A GOOD CHANCE
DYLAN COULD BE SUFFERING FROM SOMETHING PASSED DOWN TO HIM .
HAVE YOU BEEN SUFFERING FROM ANY DELUSIONAL EVENTS ,
MISS LANGENKAMP ?
MM-MMM .
THIS MAN FROM YOUR FILMS ...
FREDDY KRUEGER .
HAVE YOU BEEN SEEING HIM ?
NO .
WOULD YOU GET THOSE KEYS DOWN HERE ?
DYLAN , I WANT YOU TO STAY AWAKE .
COME ON , STAY AWAKE . KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN FOR ME .
WHERE 'S MOMMY ?
SHE 'LL BE BACK . NOW STAY AWAKE .
THERE ARE DRUGS AND TREATMENTS , MISS LANGENKAMP .
WE COULD PUT DYLAN IN FOSTER CARE FOR A SHORT WHILE .
JUST LONG ENOUGH TO RUN SOME TESTS ON YOU .
KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN . DO THAT FOR ME , OK ?
COME ON . YOU CAN STAY AWAKE .
STAY AWAKE FOR ME , DYLAN .
I WANT YOU TO STAY AWAKE , OK ?
KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN .
DYLAN , WHAT 'S THE MATTER ?
JULIE , BEHIND YOU .
THERE 'S NOTHING THERE .
DYLAN , WHAT 'S WRONG ?
DYLAN , STOP IT . YOU 'RE SCARING ME .
DYLAN .
I WANT MY SON OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW .
VERY WELL .
AS SOON AS WE CAN GATHER THE APPROPRIATE PAPERS .
YOU DON 'T UNDERSTAND .
IF DYLAN FALLS ASLEEP , THEN- -
[ JULIE SCREAMS ]
I GOT IT .
AAH !
AAH ! NO !
AAH ! DYLAN , GET OUT OF HERE !
HEY , DYLAN .
EVER PLAY SKIN THE CAT ?
Julie : OH , NO , NO !
COME ON .
HELP ME .
JULIE !
[ FREDDY LAUGHS ]
AAH !
REX !
WHAT THE HELL 'S GOING ON ?
YOU CAN 'T GO IN THERE . NO .
WAIT , WAIT .
OHH !
[ ALARM SOUNDING ]
Woman on P.A. : CODE YELLOW TO PEDIATRICS TESTING .
CODE YELLOW TO PEDIATRIC TESTING .
Heather : JULIE .
WHERE 'S MY SON ? !
WHERE IS HE ? !
HAVE YOU SEEN MY SON ?
HE WAS JUST HERE .
THE BOY . NO WAY HE 'S GOING ANYWHERE .
HE 'S BEEN HEAVILY SEDATED .
HE DOESN 'T HAVE TO BE AWAKE TO BE ON HIS FEET .
WHAT ?
HE SLEEPWALKS , YOU IDIOT .
HE 'S FULLY CAPABLE OF WALKING OUT OF THIS HOSPITAL .
OH , SHIT .
[ DIALING TELEPHONE ]
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
John : HELLO .
JOHN , IT 'S HEATHER . I NEED YOUR HELP .
WHY ? WHAT HAPPENED ?
JOHN , DYLAN 'S RUN AWAY FROM THE HOSPITAL .
I DON 'T KNOW WHETHER HE 'S WANDERING AROUND
OR HE 'S HEADED FOR THE HOUSE ,
BUT I THINK FREDDY 'S AFTER HIM .
I KNOW THAT SOUNDS SO CRAZY , BUT- -
YOU 'RE RIGHT . THAT SOUNDS CRAZY .
OH , MY GOD .
DYLAN !
Heather : YOU KNOW THAT HOME ISN 'T FAR FROM HERE , RIGHT ?
DYLAN , DYLAN !
Dylan : RIGHT ACROSS THE FREEWAY .
[ HORNS HONKING ]
[ FREDDY LAUGHING ]
DYLAN !
[ HORNS HONKING ]
[ DYLAN SCREAMING ]
KRUEGER , YOU BASTARD !
TAKE ME !
[ TRUCK HORN HONKING ]
[ DYLAN SCREAMING ]
DYLAN !
ARE YOU OK ?
YOU OK ?
Freddy : DYLAN ...
[ FREDDY LAUGHING ]
MY SON IS OUT HERE !
LET ME GO ! DYLAN !
DYLAN !
[ SIRENS ]
DYLAN .
AAH !
I 'M SORRY . WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU ?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT ?
I 'M FINE . HAVE YOU SEEN DYLAN ?
TAKE IT EASY , TAKE IT EASY .
RELAX . HE 'S RIGHT THERE . WHAT HAPPENED ?
OH , DYLAN .
OH , GOD .
John : WHAT 'S GOING ON , HEATHER ?
WHAT IN THE WORLD HAPPENED ?
I KNOW HOW CHASE REALLY DIED .
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
FRED KRUEGER DID IT .
YEAH . SURE .
YOU SAW HIM , DIDN 'T YOU ?
♪ COMING FOR YOU
John : NANCY , LET 'S GO OUTSIDE .
DYLAN .
HE 'LL BE ALL RIGHT .
I 'LL BE RIGHT BACK .
[ SCRAPE ]
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON , NANCY ?
WHY ARE YOU CALLING ME NANCY , JOHN ?
WHY ARE YOU CALLING ME JOHN ?
[ POLICE RADIO CRACKLES ]
NANCY , PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER
BEFORE YOU MAKE YOURSELF AND THAT KID NUTS .
JOHN !
WOULD YOU CALL ROBERT ?
ROBERT ?
ROBERT ENGLUND .
YOU KNOW , THE GUY WHO PLAYS FREDDY .
FREDDY WHO ?
FREDDY KRUEGER .
NANCY , FREDDY 'S DEAD .
DON 'T START LOSING IT LIKE YOUR MOTHER DID .
I LOVE YOU , SWEETHEART .
DON 'T FORGET THAT .
I LOVE YOU , TOO ...
DADDY .
GET YOURSELF SOME REST , NANCY , PLEASE .
[ CAR STARTS ]
DYLAN !
Dylan : ♪ 1 , 2 , FREDDY 'S COMING FOR YOU ♪
Freddy : WHO 'S THERE ?
T.V. : LISTEN , DADDY . I 'VE GOT A PROPOSITION FOR YOU .
I 'M GONNA GO AND GET THE GUY WHO DID IT ,
AND I WANT YOU TO BE THERE TO ARREST HIM
WHEN I BRING HIM OUT , OK ?
John : NANCY , JUST TELL ME WHO DID IT .
I 'LL GO GET HIM , BABY .
FRED KRUEGER DID IT , DADDY .
YEAH , SURE .
DYLAN 'S SLEEPING PILLS .
Dylan 's voice : SAY HOW THEY FIND THEIR WAY BACK HOME .
IT 'S IMPORTANT .
BREADCRUMBS .
DYLAN !
Freddy : TOO LATE , HEATHER .
TOO LATE .
Heather : DYLAN .
DYLAN .
JOIN YOU .
YOU 'VE GIVEN ME A WAY TO JOIN YOU .
YES .
Dylan : MOMMY !
AAH !
[ CLANG ]
Dylan : MOMMY !
DYLAN !
[ ECHOES ]
[ CLANG ]
Dylan : MOMMY !
[ FREDDY LAUGHS ]
Freddy : ALMOST THERE .
" THE MORE SHE READ , THE MORE SHE REALIZED
" WHAT SHE HAD IN HER HANDS WAS NOTHING MORE OR LESS
" THAN HER LIFE ITSELF .
" THAT EVERYTHING SHE HAD EXPERIENCED AND THOUGHT
WAS BOUND WITHIN THESE PAGES . "
[ CLANG ]
" THERE WAS NO MOVIE .
THERE WAS ONLY ... HER LIFE . "
AAH !
IT 'S JUST ME . DYLAN .
ARE YOU OK ? ARE YOU ALL RIGHT ?
YEAH .
OK , WHERE 'S THE MAN ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
HE HAD ME ,
BUT THEN HE LET ME GO .
AAH !
MEET YOUR MAKER .
PICK A PET FOR THE RUGRAT , BITCH .
AAH !
FUCK YOU !
MOMMY !
Heather : GET OVER THERE , DYLAN !
AAH !
TAKE THIS !
COME HERE , MY PIGGY .
I GOT SOME GINGERBREAD FOR YOU .
NO !
MOMMY !
GOTCHA !
HA !
MOMMY .
MOMMY !
Freddy : MOMMY !
Freddy : WHERE 'S YOUR MOMMY , PIGLET , HUH , HUH ?
Freddy : 1 , 2 , FREDDY 'S COMING FOR YOU !
[ SCREECH ]
DYLAN !
Dylan : MOMMY !
AAH !
COME TO PAPA .
AAAAH !
GONNA EAT YOU UP .
LEAVE HIM ALONE !
[ HISSING ]
DYLAN , GET OUT OF THERE !
HEY !
AAH !
PUSH !
RUN !
ARE YOU OK ?
YEAH .
HONEY , HONEY .
OH , MY GOD .
WE 'RE SAVED . THE WITCH IS DEAD .
AND HIS MOTHER COVERED HIM WITH KISSES ,
AND THEY WERE SAFE .
Wes : " HEATHER- - THANKS FOR HAVING THE GUTS
" TO PLAY NANCY ONE LAST TIME .
" AT LAST FREDDY 'S BACK WHERE HE BELONGS .
REGARDS , WES . "
IS IT A STORY ?
YEAH .
IT 'S A STORY .
READ ME SOME .
" WE OPEN ON AN OLD WOODEN BENCH .
" THERE 'S FIRE AND TOOLS
" AND A MAN 'S GRIMY HANDS BUILDING
" WHAT SOON IS REVEALED AS A GLEAMING SET OF CLAWS .
" AND THE CLAWS ARE MOVING NOW ,
" AS IF AWAKENING FROM A LONG AND UNWANTED SLEEP .
" THEN THE MAN LAYS ONE TREMBLING HAND FLAT UPON THE TABLE ,
" AND WITH HIS OTHER PICKS UP A THICK , SHARP BLADE .
" BEHIND THE LIGHTS , FACES WATCH FROM THE DARKNESS- -
READY TO LAUGH OR SCREAM IN TERROR . "
♪ 1 , 2
♪ FREDDY 'S COMING FOR YOU
♪ 3 , 4
♪ BETTER LOCK YOUR DOOR
♪ 5 , 6
♪ GRAB YOUR CRUCIFIX
♪ 7 , 8
♪ BETTER STAY UP LATE
♪ 9 , 10
♪ NEVER SLEEP AGAIN